Hello everyone! I'm Mizuki Oshina and S Mi Lennon from Niyagikorejoy!
Today is the first recording to commemorate the fact that we are the Niyagi-Joi Ilamen club!
Yay!
Lennon is here for the first time!
First time on the list!
Thank you very much!
The NyaJoi Lahmen Club is a group of NyaJoi members who love to get together and work together.
It is a group of NyaJoi members who especially love ramen.
I, Mizuki Ooshii, am the first member of this club.
And I am the first member of the club.
By the way, I think the Ikonoiju Museum is now open.
You can make name stickers there.
We made a recording called "Nya-Joi Ilamen Club".
I hope you all enjoy it!
Please try to make one!
Today's project...
As this is the first time we've done this
We're going to see how many bowls of kaidama we can eat together.
I've never eaten to the limit, probably.
Usually.
So let's see how far we can go.
Let's test the limits!
Let us know our limits!
Let's get to it!
Let's go!
I'm going to go buy ramen in the restaurant.
Okay, now I'm going to buy my ramen from the ticket machine.
Let's buy!
First, I'm going to buy a standard ramen
Oh, great, I almost bought it
Oh, great.
You can choose the green onions and stuff at your table, so just this once?
Okay, here you go.
I'm going to eat my ramen with this.
I bought it!
Yay!Yay!
I'm going to buy ramen in the store!
I want it to be a little thick because it's the first time I've ever had it, and I want it to be a little red because it's a red day!
What a book! I like my noodles hard!
That's me!
It's good!
You'll have to present it in there.
The thickness of the flavor is basic.
The richness of the flavor is the basic.
Garlic is basic
The green onion is white onion
There is chashu pork
The sauce is normal.
The hardness of the noodle is the only thing I prefer, so I set it to hard.
As for me...
I like the flavor to be strong and the richness to be light.
A little bit of garlic
The green onion is white onion and there is chashu pork.
The noodles are soft.
You're not used to saying that, are you?
I'm a bit of a regular.
I'm not a regular at all.
Excuse me, please.
Thank you.
I'm really curious.
I hear it's amazing.
What's this?
I'll drink to that.
To water.
I'd like to make a toast with water.
First of all, I'd like to make a toast.
Let's have a toast.
Cheers.
Cheers!
You did a great job today.Sure worked hard today.
Good luck.
Delicious.
And what?
Let me introduce you to the rear dahmooms.
First of all, Mr. Director, Mitsuki.
It's just a formality.
And this is club member 1.
Member #1.
Commemorative.
We've been friends behind the scenes for a long time.
And Juli.
Not Juli.
But it still means Juli's coming.
Here she comes. Here she comes.
Oh, my God.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
Be careful, it's hot.
Bon appétit.
Oh, man.
Should I mix these? The red one.
Yes, you should mix it a little.
Oh, my God, there's so much fat.
It's very fatty.
I'll go light.
Bon appétit.
Yum!
Yum! Yum!
Can I have three cups?
I think I can make it three.
But only if we're late.
Yeah. - Yeah.Yup.
Delicious!
You know, before...
With Yuuka and Juli.
Yes, yes, yes.
When we got married.
We couldn't go because it was closed. It was crowded.
We both eat.
No one talks.
That's it. Where do we go?
You know, just the two of us.
Zzzzzz!
When we go out to eat ramen together, we don't talk, right?
I'm too absorbed in my ramen.
I've been listening to my uncle's stories from my forehead the whole time.
He's eating the whole time.
He's eating so much, the back of his head is moving.
He's been eating without any money.
I'm sure, this is a real daily routine.
I'll just put it up.
Thank you very much.
I don't know if I have a particular favorite ramen or not.
Tempura
So much tempura!
That's an excuse!
But I'm just making excuses to eat tonk tempura!
You know what?
It's so white!
White is cool!
But I like miso ramen the best.
That's one reason I eat miso so much.
It's like soy sauce with miso.
It's like shoyu tonkotsu.
Shoyu and tonkotsu.
It's exactly the same.
I can't believe it.I'm going to turn it upside down
Description.
Did you eat it by any chance?
It was a pain in the ass.
May I say kaid mai?
Thank you.
But I'm not out of lemons.
Let's go.
Can I go?
Yeah, I'm going up the stairs.
I'll go up the stairs too.
Does that mean I don't have to eat?
You mean I shouldn't?
They had salmon roe.
Here you go.
Oh, my God, they're here.
They're here.
This is the way to the other side.
Hard, hard!
Look, it's got sauce on it!
Oh, my God!
It's got flavor! Isn't it amazing?
How much is that?
I ordered kikurage too.
Are you sure you want to eat this?
Eat it. Do what you want.
Really? Are you in heaven right now?
I don't know... a lot of your fans like ramen, too.
You know, there are a lot of people who like ramen.
Some of them send me ramen at night or something.
I see that... they often come here for ramen.
They come!
Eat ramen the next day for sure!
I'll definitely come!
Where do they keep coming?
They'll be gone soon!I'm going to run out soon!
This is the first time I ate ramen as I wanted.
That's fast!
So fast!
The noodles are so good!
Look at this!
Here it is.
Thank you.
Yes, please.
Second bowl?
The second bowl of kaidama.
It's like a ramen.
I want one of these at home.
No, I want a bowl.
I really want one of these.
What would you make?
Let's see...
Tenshindon.
Oh, that's good. Tenshinhan.
I've had Tenshinhan.
Can you make it? Tenshindon.
I can make it.
I can make pretty much anything.
Like chahan?
I can make chahan.
That's great.
I'm pretty sure it'll be mushy, but chahan...
What? Why?
I don't know.
It's kind of dry.
What was that?
You should cook the eggs first.
Eggs first?
Put the eggs in first.
Then you put the rice on top of the eggs.
And wow.If you do it with a "wow" sound
It's gonna be floppy.
Flatten?
What's wrong with eggs? Don't they burn?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, let's try it.
It's really good.
You guys should try it.
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up.
It's like cooking.
Yeah, that's what he said.
We'll talk about it at the next meeting.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
Second cup?
Second cup.
Second bowl is ready.
But, you know, it's actually the third bowl of noodles.
That's for sure.
Which is it? Does that count as the first bowl of noodles for you, Kainaman?
Or is this the third bowl of noodles?
Which is it?
Three.
So it's the third one.
Oh, you've eaten a lot, haven't you?
Yeah, I've had a lot.
You're gonna hit your target.
Yeah, because, you know...
They've been filming for 30 minutes.
What?
He eats a noodle every minute.
Wow! I've never had ramen like this.
I know, right?
Yes, and the shape of the noodles.Yeah, and the shape of the noodles.
I tried the basic.
It's good basic.
It's different from hard noodles.
Yeah, it's different.
Harder noodles are harder.
Looks expensive.
I finished it.
I'm done.
You lost a lot of kikurage mushrooms in one go.
Isn't it bad?
I love kikurage.
Thank you.
How many?
Four?
Four!
Not even close!
Super soft and basic.
This is super soft.
This is hard.
Hard?
That's totally different!
That's amazing.
It looks so hard!
I don't have a strong jaw.
You don't have a strong jaw?
It's a man!
Oh, my God!
Look at this!
Why do you do it like that?
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
You've got me!
It's mind-blowing.
I see.I see.
If I eat this, I'm totally on target.
8 for two?
Eight.
Oh, no.
I'm getting a little full.
I guess four is the limit, huh?
Yeah.
That's not good.
Chin.
I'm gonna try that one.
Hmm?
Yeah, well.
Ha-ha-ha.
Looks tight.
I'm doing some kind of protective gear show. There's a standing up thing.
You want to get up and do it with me? We'll do it together.
Stand up, and then you can actually do it with your stomach.
Mmm-hmm. Mmm-hmm. Mmm-hmm.
Like this? That's what I'm doing now.
Oh, my God. Isn't that fast? Pickle.
It's a little easier.
Oh, shit.
I'll just put Anitov in there.
Excuse me.
Excuse me?
I'm having anitofu.
You don't splurge?
I've never been this extravagant at a ramen restaurant.
It's the first time.
Not at a regular ramen store.
You know how I've had ramen with twice the noodles and twice the ingredients?
I wonder which is better.
Which one? This one?
It's like a work of art.
Wow.Oh, wow.
Looks like Mt.
It's a work of art.
It's a bit... it's a bit... it's a bit of a standard.
It's not even close.
I ordered the apricot bean curd!
A work of art!
It's Mt.
Speaking of Masa
Yuuka
Just in case
I don't need it
Yuka-chan is...
Yuka is...
You know what?
On the radio.
On the radio, I talked about a subject like, "If we were to create a club in Miyagi
I talked about it.
At that time
I thought it would be great to have a ramen club.
Anyway, it was me.
I wrote down all the people I've mentioned.
Me.
Yuka Murayama...
That was it, wasn't it?
After coming to Tokyo...
It's been a year and a half.
Oh, no.
She said she hadn't eaten in a year and a half.
It's really not the music video with the big sky.
I know.
And yet...
I wrote "ramen club.
Yuka-chan, too.
You're a dame, aren't you?I know, it's dumb.
I'm in it.
I don't eat ramen.
What about Alice?
Do you eat ramen with Alice?
Yes, I do.
But Alice...
Alice probably doesn't eat ramen either.
And yet you wrote this.
I've only mentioned Miyagi, by the way.
Anyone can come in.
Look at this!
That's a lot of food.
Finished? Noodles
Noodles.
The letters are Lovell.
Noodles
I made a mistake.
Sorry.
I meant what I said.
I made a mistake.
It's getting tighter and tighter.
Well, we're only human.
It's been a while.
I think I ate a lot of food.
How can you say that?
I used to...
There are days when you don't organize your meals.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like, for a concert or something.
I can't tell you what period I'm in.
I wrote it today.
It's true.
I wonder if he's saying it.
No, I'm not.
Well... now...Let's see, now.
This dog doctor
before
But, no, not really...
This dog doctor is already stuck in front of me.
I mean, it's almost there.
We're doing what we want.
We're getting lovey-dovey.
Is it okay? Who am I?
Ramen noodles are kind of...
I'll try to say it.
Rice doesn't make you fat.
Yeah.
Wise words from Mizuki.
Rice is not fattening.
You will gain weight.
You'll lose weight if you sleep.
You won't lose weight
You'll lose weight.
You won't lose weight.
Oh! You're so beautiful.
Oh, my God.
How many have you had?
Four!
I just had 4 ramen!
I finished them!
I had the first one, then 2, 3, 4, and 4.
It was delicious!
Well, I'm glad I was able to finish them!
If you, the viewers, can tell me how much you can eat, or how many bowls you ate the most, I would love to hear your comments!
Also, I usually get a lot of tips from you, but if you have any recommendations, please let me know in the comments!
Please tell us! Please let me know!Please tell us! Please!
So, that's all for now, Niyajoiler members!
Bye bye! Thank you very much!